Have you got an addictive nature?
你有容易上瘾的天性吗？
Are you unable to stop yourself joining in with the latest obsession for collecting or doing something?
你是否无法阻止自己参与到最新的对收藏或做某事的痴迷中呢？
This probably describes most of us because it's only human nature to not want to miss out on something that everyone else is talking about.
这可能描述了我们大多数人，因为不想错过其他人都在谈论的事情只是人的本性而已。
Most fads arrive suddenly and enthusiasm for them spreads quickly.
大多数时尚潮流突然出现，人们对它们的热情迅速蔓延。
They become a talking point on social media; we read about them, give them a try and, before we know it, we are hooked.
它们成为社交媒体上的热点话题；我们读到相关内容，尝试一下，不知不觉中，我们就上瘾了。
In the past, these have been objects such as toys and games.
在过去，这些潮流涉及的物品有玩具和游戏等。
Maybe you were the proud owner of a Rubik's cube, which became the best-selling toy of all time - around 350 million have been sold so far.
也许你曾骄傲地拥有魔方，它是有史以来最畅销的玩具——到目前为止已售出约3.5亿个。
Now, technology is driving the latest crazes.
如今，科技推动着最新的热潮。
In some parts of the world, flavour of the month is Pokémon Go - a game that uses augmented reality, where little virtual monsters pop up onto your phone and you have to catch them.
在世界的一些地方，当下的热门事物是《精灵宝可梦Go》——一款使用增强现实技术的游戏，虚拟的小怪物会突然出现在你的手机上，你必须捕捉它们。
And games such as Angry Birds and Minecraft are other crazes, available on smartphones and tablets, that have been hard to put down.
像《愤怒的小鸟》和《我的世界》等游戏也很流行，可在智能手机和平板电脑上玩，让人爱不释手。
Our keenness to participate in crazes has been analysed by experts.
专家们分析了我们参与热潮的热情。
One of them, Dr Ben Michaelis, a clinical psychologist, explains that we want to experience the benefit that another person, or group of people, have experienced from something and this "hooks into an ancient evolutionary fear of being left behind or abandoned by our tribes"; we have to join in or lose out.
其中一位专家，临床心理学家本·米歇利斯博士解释说，我们想要体验其他人或群体从某事物中体验到的益处，这与一种古老的进化演变的恐惧有关，即害怕被我们的部落遗留或抛弃；我们必须参与其中，否则就会遗憾出局。
Although becoming addicted to a computer game might not seem like a 'benefit', it can at least give you credibility or popularity among your friends.
尽管沉迷于电脑游戏可能看起来不像是一种“益处”，但它至少能让你在朋友中获得可信度或人气。
It allows you to learn new skills and gives you something to talk about at parties!
它能让你学到新技能，并且在聚会上有话题可聊！
But fashions come and go and most fads are just a flash in the pan so if one of them is not your cup of tea, don't worry: there'll be a new craze arriving very soon.
但是时尚潮流来来去去，大多数潮流只是昙花一现，所以如果其中一个不是你感兴趣的事物，别担心：很快就会有新的潮流出现。
Look at the addiction to the unsophisticated loom bands — those little rubber bands you could make jewellery and other things out of.
看看对简易的编织带的痴迷——就是那些可以用来制作首饰和其他东西的小橡皮筋。
For a brief period they were the must-have item for any schoolchild, now they're the bargain bucket item in a discount shop or worse still, trash filling up our landfill sites!
在一段时间内，它们是每个学生的必备物品，现在它们成了折扣店的廉价商品，更糟糕的是，它们成了填满垃圾填埋场的垃圾！
What crazes have you been addicted to?
你曾经对什么潮流上瘾过呢？